+98 (933) 618-6568 Fariborz.js@gmail.com

Fariborz Shalghooni

Summary

Front-End Developer with more than **4 years of experience** in front-end programming using **React JS – Next JS** technologies - has complete and sufficient mastery of the necessary tools and knowledge for the mentioned technologies, including:

FrontEnd Skills: Tailwind CSS - Type Script - WEB3 -React Material UI - TanStack Query - Zustand-Redux - Graph QL- Axios -REST Api - NextUi lib - Shadcn lib - SOLID & Front-End Design Patterns - UI/UX - SCRUM & Agile

Web3Modal(SDK) – viem (web3 lib) – wagmi (web3 lib) Telegram Bot (Nestjs) – Telegram MiniApp (Nextjs)

Backend Skills: Nestjs -Postgress -Nodejs

INTRESTED IN: StartUp - ML - chess - problem solving - book - startup ecosystem.

Skill Highlights

- Knowledge of ES6, TypeScript, HTML, SCSS
- TanStack Query Zustand -Redux
- TWA PWA Responsive Design UI/UX
- Web 3 MetaMask TronLink (DApp)
- Web3Modal(SDK) viem (web3 lib) –
 Wagmi (web3 lib) –
- Gsap Lenis

- ReactJS NextJS
- Tailwind Css
- Graph QL REST Api
- OOP Design Patterns Clean Code
- ShadCn NextUi MDUi AntD
- Telegram Bot (Nestjs) Telegram MiniApp (Nextjs)

Experience

WEB3 Front-End Developer (Remote) - 07/2023 to 04/2024

Exmodule company, IRAN, MASHAHAD

- WEB3 Front End NecxtJs Developer
- Development of DX exchange websites
- Develop and connection with contract and Metamask or Tronlink on any network
- Develop Attractive UI

Team lead Front-End Developer (Remote) - 09/2020 to 04/2023

Silver Age, IRAN, MASHAHAD

- Front End Team Lead
- Creating and developing a dedicated infrastructure based on NEXTJS to reduce the time
 of producing templates in this framework, which separated the logic part from the UI
 and helped us to reduce the time of developing new templates by 70%.

- Design and Architecture the company products and extra projects.
- Code review and code refactor of Front end team members

Front-End Developer (Remote-Part time) - 09/2021 to 06/2022

Rootip.io, United Kingdom, London

- 30% development of Back-End by Express.js NodeJS
- 50% development of Front-End by Next JS React JS
- Create development document for **Back-End and Front-End**
- UI/UX base design

Education

Bachelor of Science: Computer Software Engineer – 2023 Islamic Azad university-Gonbad

Languages

Persian (native) Azeri (native) English (mid)